NGUYEN THI THANH MAI

Front-end developer

mainguyency@gmail.com

© 0395067721

6 09/21/1999

♀ Thuan Thanh district, Bac Ninh

SUMMARY

I'm a Front-end developer with 2+ years of experience in Web and Mobile development. I have almost one year of experience building mobile financial applications with React Native and 1+ year of experience building management systems using the company's low-code platform. I with my team successfully deployed HDBank's Back Office system on time and received high praise.

With my knowledge and skills, I'm confident that my abilities will contribute to the success of many projects company. By working collaboratively with the team, I can ensure we deliver high-quality results that meet the needs of both the company and the client.

SKILLS

Technologies:

- JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS
- React Native, ReactJS, React Query, Bootstrap, Tailwind
- Git, Rest API

Tools:

GitHub, Jira, XCode, Android Studio, Figma

Others:

- Good communication with clients
- Experience leading team
- Teamwork/Personal skills are good
- Reading and understanding documents in English
- 530 TOEIC (2021 2023).

EXPERIENCE

Front-end Developer

03/2022 - now

Nuclent Pte. Ltd.

- Design metadata similar to a database, and develop functions and web app management based on clients and company requirements.
- Communicate directly with customers in building functions for the client's system, support, reproduce bugs, fix bugs on the core platform, and notify the dev platforms team.
- Using JavaScript and ReactJS to build the logic, feature, and interface application if the system is not supported.
- Cooperate with members in teams, QA, and parties to develop project functions using React Native on IOS, and Android platforms.
- Upgrade and maintain the app, and add functions when required by customers.

HDBank's Back Office

Sep 2023 - Mar 2024

- Description: A process system that handles the behind-the-scenes administrative and operational tasks, supporting the smooth functioning of customer-facing transactions. Build in the company's low-code platform. Includes: Financial accounts, Record keeping, Ensuring the smooth transfer, and Risk management,...
- Role: The lead team dev, Developer
- Management Process: Scrum
- Responsibilities:
 - o In the first phase (2 months): The lead team dev, divides tasks for the team
 - o Analysis, design metadata similar to a database, and development features, flow, and UI.
 - o Receive bugs, fix bugs, and notify the dev platforms team.
 - Using JavaScript and ReactJS to build the logic, feature, and interface application if the system is not supported.
- Technologies: Javascript, ReactJS, and features in the low-code platform
- **Team size:** 3 5 members developer

Nuclent mobile app Mar 2022 - Jan 2023

• **Description**: A personal finance management application is a software tool designed to help individuals manage their money effectively. Includes: Tracking Income and Expenses, Budgeting, Goal Setting and Tracking, and Money transfers,...

- Role: Front-end Developer
- Responsibilities:
 - Rebuild according to the new design and divide the main functions that could be shared into small modules to reuse similar mobile devices.
 - o Develop specialized functions based on task
 - o Cooperate with members in teams, QA, and parties to develop project functions
 - Upgrade and maintain the app, and add functions when required by customers.
- Technologies: React Native, React Query, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, and some libraries
- **Team size**: about 5 members

EDUCATION

Posts and Telecommunications Institute of Technology

2017 - 2022

Information Technology (Information System)

Degree classification: Good